{
	"Quiz" : [
		{"question" : "Electrons are larger than molecules.", "answer" : "false", "type" : "truefalse"},
		{"question" : "The Atlantic Ocean is the biggest ocean on Earth.", "answer" : "false", "type" : "truefalse"},
		{"question" : "The chemical make up food often changes when you cook it.", "answer" : "true", "type" : "truefalse"},
		{"question" : "Sharks are mammals.", "answer" : "false", "type" : "truefalse"},
		{"question" : "The human body has four lungs.", "answer" : "false", "type" : "truefalse"},
		{"question" : "Atoms are most stable when their outer shells are full.", "answer" : "true", "type" : "truefalse"},
		{"question" : "Filtration separates mixtures based upon their particle size.", "answer" : "true", "type" : "truefalse"},
		{"question" : "Venus is the closest planet to the Sun.Conductors have low resistance.", "answer" : "false", "type" : "truefalse"},
		{"question" : "Conductors have low resistance.", "answer" : "true", "type" : "truefalse"},
		{"question" : "Molecules can have atoms from more than one chemical element.", "answer" : "true", "type" : "truefalse"},
		{"question" : "Water is an example of a chemical element.", "answer" : "false", "type" : "truefalse"},
	]
	
}